sexxxcafe.com 2013-06-30

# Sexxxcafe.com - Privacy Policy

**1\. Applicable to Sexxxcafe Services**

By using or visiting the Sites or using the Sexxxcafe Services, You agree to the collection and use of information by us in accordance with the terms of this policy ("Privacy Policy"). If You do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Sites or the Sexxxcafe Services.

**2\. Minors Not Eligible to Use Our Service**

The Sites expressly and strictly limit membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet this criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of the Sites. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from minors and minors may not lawfully visit the Sites or use the Sexxxcafe services. See the Sexxxcafe Terms of Service. 

**3\. Types of Information**

**Personally Identifiable Information (PII).** PII is information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card information, video materials that you submit, comments you make including such information, or other information that you submit voluntarily, including, but not limited to, when you contact us by email. 

The Sites do not collect PII from users except for email addresses in limited cases: 

  1. User submits feedback to the Sites.
  2. User sends the Sites a support-related email.

The Sites absolutely do not distribute user email addresses to third party vendors unless necessary to solve a user-submitted support ticket. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII).** Non-PII is information that does not identify you as an individual including but not limited to your browser type, language, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser cookies, operating system, the date and time of your request, and the types of services you use. 

**4\. When Do We Collect Information**

**Browsing the Sexxxcafe Services.** You can view free videos or browse content using the Sexxxcafe Services without registering as a user. You can also contact us at info@Sexxxcafe.com or other Site email addresses without having to register for a user name. We do not collect PII when you are only browsing the Sites or the Sexxxcafe Services, but we may associate certain information about your use of the Sexxxcafe Services with your IP address and/or session id. Such information may include the categories of videos that you view, the information about categorization that you provide to us, or your ratings of videos all in order to provide you with a better overall experience. 

**Emails.** If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. When you send us feedback email, we attach certain Non-PII to the email to help the Site troubleshoot your request. 

**Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g., the name, face or likeness of you or others depicted in videos) or any link that you provide with your video submission or information you disclose in comments you make in response to videos may be collected and used by others. 

**5\. How Do We Collect Information?**

**Cookies.** A cookie is a message that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We may use cookies to assist in (a) helping you stay logged on the Site (b) adding videos to quicklist or (c) saving videos to history.

_We use cookies only for the operation of the Sexxxcafe Services._

**IP Address.** An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer automatically when you use the Internet. We may collect IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration, server problem diagnosis and to compile aggregate information (such as how many visitors visited the Site and their approximate geographic locations). When you visit a particular Web page on the Site, our servers log your IP address. We analyze aggregated user traffic information to improve the quality of the user-experience. 

**6\. Your Role in Protecting Your Privacy**

Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any password you use to register, and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online. Without limitation of the foregoing, please keep your username and password private and safe. 

**7\. Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

If you use the Sexxxcafe Services, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and we will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Sexxxcafe Services. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Sites or the Sexxxcafe Services after we either personally notify you or generally post such changes on the site will constitute your acceptance of those changes. If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at info@Sexxxcafe.com.
